# Autumn Cummings Graphic Designer

Contact:

autumn.makenzie.cummings@gmail.com 401-500-1346



#### **About Me**

I am a motivated individual who has always had a love for the arts, but definitely found my calling in high school when I was introduced to the world of graphic design. Seeing a client's reaction to a design is one of my favorite experiences in the world knowing I was able to make their ideas a reality.

### **Skills**

**Hard Skills** 

Proficient in
Adobe Programs
Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, InDesign
Screen Printing
Logo Design
Poster Design
Color Theory

Soft Skills
Communication
Team Work
Work Ethic
Creativity
Adaptability

Listening

#### **Education**

<u>University of Massachusetts Dartmouth</u> BFA Graphic Design Expected Graduation: May 2023

<u>Attleboro High School</u> Graphic Design & Communications Graduated: May 2019

## **Work Experience**

Attleboro YMĈA - Attleboro, MA Lifeguard, August 2017 - Present

Rue 21 - North Attleboro, MA Sales Associate, August 2018 - August 2019 Cahier, August 2018 - August 2019

<u>Mediterranean Grill and Pizzeria</u> - Attleboro, MA Busser, February 2016 - July 2017 Hostess, July 2016 - July 2017

#### Volunteer Work

<u>St. Theresa of Child Jesus Parish</u> - Attleboro, MA CCD Office Aide, July 2014 - July 2015

<u>Tsunami Swim Team</u>, Attleboro - MA Swim Meet Coach Assistant, Seasonal